Joshua O'Brien

Columbus, OH 43232 joshuaobrien28@yahoo.com +1 614 980 1488

Creative and resourceful Project and Retail Manager with 13 years of employee development, project management, and customer service experience. I am great at problem solving while being particularly skilled at building effective relationships. I'm always invested in the financial needs of the company by thinking outside the box about how we could be more efficient. I am seeking a challenging new position that along with hard work and an excellent brand will be a valuable asset to you and this company.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Geek Squad Manager

Best Buy - Dublin, OH September 2021 to Present

Run the day to day business for all in store services (geek squad precinct and auto-bay). I assist in problem solving through windows / Macintosh protocols, as well as managing client experiences including Management issues. Continuously building future solutions for my customers and employees.

Omni Channel (Retail) Supervisor

BEST BUY LLC - Dublin, OH October 2020 to August 2021

Manage all areas of the store including sales and operations. Responsible for developing and managing a staff of around 50 employees, coaching and training making sure quarterly and daily goals are met.

Project Team - Project deployment Supervisor / Manager

BEST BUY LLC - Dublin, OH March 2012 to October 2020

Organized employees along with contractors through leadership on several multi-million dollar remodels and special "one off" deployment projects. I work with corporate partners, vendors and clients keeping everyone up to date on schedule changes and project feedback.

Education

High school or equivalent in Project Management

Reynoldsburg High School - Reynoldsburg, OH September 2004 to May 2008

Skills

- Effective communication
- · Approachable and encouraging
- Drive company goals that lead to company growth. (Met goals in a timely manner)
- Dedicated to constantly improve
- Everyone is welcome, and everyone has a role to play.
- I have been invited to corporate meetings and nominated for countless awards in current position.
- Employee Viewpoints survey was one of the highest in the company at 98% (3 Years running)
- · Microsoft Office
- Management
- Organizational Skills
- Developmental Training
- Program Management
- · Project coordination
- Project management software
- · Retail Management
- · Project Management
- · Microsoft SharePoint
- Data entry
- Typing
- Adobe Analytics
- Marketing
- Social listening
- · Cloud architecture
- Microservices
- E-commerce
- · Analysis skills
- Design patterns
- Construction
- Web Services
- Power BI
- · Distributed control systems

Assessments

Sales: Influence & Negotiation — Expert

January 2020

Persuading reluctant customers to buy products or services, and influencing and negotiating with customers to meet sales goals.

Full results: Expert

Supervisory Skills: Directing Others — Highly Proficient

January 2020

Motivating others to achieve objectives and identifying improvements or corrective actions.

Full results: <u>Highly Proficient</u>

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.